Es hora de decir adiós.
What do you mean goodbye?
Oh, it's not what it looks like.
No, no, no.
It's exactly what it looks like.
By the way, did you know that
lieutenant Columbo was
my favorite character of all time?
One more thing.
You realized you
couldn't have children
but instead of admitting that
you started blaming Gina, right?
That's nonsense.
Hey.
Hey, that's still my part.
No, no, no.
Things just didn't
go as you planned, right?
Gina was too kind,
and she left you herself.
She couldn't bear the idea
of not giving you a child,
and you decided to tie her
to you another way -
by keeping her mom
in a coma, right?
These are just your
wild accusations.
I extended her mother's life.
Gina had a whole year
to come to terms
with her loss.
Until I found someone
to buy her organs.
Where is my patient?